Requirements: High Level

Helpful Narrator Tool
	Shows current state of game (secret from players): how many wolves/townspeople remain, what powers remain
	Provides functions for narrator to enter who is targeted/silenced/killed, etc. during each night
	Updates state of game as the play continues, and displays relevant information to the narrator
	When one side has won, states that the game is over and displays statistics

In-Game Stats 
	The app will allow for the town to view current game stats that are non-secret
	Non-secret info can include who has died, who is mayor, who is nominated for death, etc.

Persistent Stats
	The app will contain functionality that keeps statistics on players
	Names can be stored, along with simple profiles/bios and portraits
	Player profiles will be used for simple entry when setting up a game
	Statistics kept:
		Wins as a townsperson / times as a townsperson
		Wins as a wolf / times as a wolf
		Elections to mayor
		Powers acquired / powers used