Werewolf App v1.0

Players

Setup Phase

Name Entry
	Allow for entry of new player names into the app data store to be used in games.

Choose Players
	When a new game is started, choose players from the data store for the new game.

Assign Roles
	Once player names are chosen for the game, roles are randomly assigned to each player. Allow for a variable number of wolves.  

Game Phase

Day Phase - "The town awakens."
UI: List of player names, with role and attribute next to them (Dead, Silenced, Alive)
Deliberation
	All players deliberate over the true identities of the Werewolves. 

Nomination - "Player X has been nominated by Player Y."
	Players nominate other players to be considered for execution. Any player can nominate, and any player can be nominated.

Voting - "Player X has been killed by the town."
	Players vote on the nominees. All players must vote, and there is no no-kill option. In the event of a tie, a second vote occurs. In the event of a second tie, both players are killed.

Night Phase - "The town goes to sleep."
Alpha - Silence: "Alpha Werewolf, who will you silence tonight?"

Wolves - Kill: "Wolves, who will you kill tonight?"

Seer - Investigate: "Seer, who will you investigate tonight?"

Witch - Save / Kill: "Witch, will you save this person tonight?" / "Witch, who, if anyone, will you kill tonight?"


Results Phase

